<questions>
    <question>
        <statement>What kind of music do you play?</statement>
        <answer>It varies. We're a large group compared to most chamber music groups, so we have been able to play symphonies with additional guest instruments, but we've also played music written for string quartet. Per concert we usually cover a range of time periods, from Baroque to contemporary music.</answer>
        <note>You may check out our concerts page for more details on our previous repertoire.</note>
    </question>
    <question>
        <statement>What skill level do you play at?</statement>
        <answer>We are a non-audition group so the skill level required is much lower than other audition groups at Hart House. The pieces we play varies in skill level. You can take a look at our concerts section for the names of pieces we have performed in the past or you can attend our open rehearsal which takes place at the beginning of each semester.</answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <statement>Do I need my own intrument to join?</statement>
        <answer>Yes, you do. You can rent one at various places in Toronto if you don't have your instrument with you at UofT, but we don't have any instruments for you that you can borrow. A good place to start your search for either renting or buying an instrument is The Soundpost, which specializes in bowed string instruments and is located near the Queen's Park subway station.</answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <statement>Is there a membership fee?</statement>
        <answer>Yes, the Hart House Chamber Strings Orchestra has a membership fee. This fee can vary from year to year and changes if you are a student. Find membership information on our membership page.</answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <statement>Are there any requirements to join as a non-student member?</statement>
        <answer>Non-student members may have to pay an additional fee page) but other than that, there are no other requirements for non-students, and we do have many members who are not students.</answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <statement>Can I still join the Hart House Chamber Strings if I missed the open rehearsal?</statement>
        <answer>You can still join if you missed the open rehearsal. Just come to the next rehearsal with your instrument. If you have missed more than two rehearsals, please contact your section leader for more information.</answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <statement>I was unable to join in the fall semester, can I still join in the winter semester?</statement>
        <answer>If you were unable to join us for the first concert, you can still join us for the following concert, and you only have to pay for the second term. Our first rehearsal after the Winter Concert (and winter break) is January 7, 2019.</answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <statement>How should I contact the Hart House Chamber Strings?</statement>
        <answer>Please see below :)</answer>
    </question>
</questions>